Forrest "Bud" Harris Photographs, ca. 1950s-2007 AIS.2013.05
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Forrest "Bud" Harris Photographs
ca. 1950s-2007
1960-1999
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Harris, Bud
AIS.2013.05
20 Linear Feet (80 boxes)
Forrest "Bud" Harris was a commercial and advertising photographer. Born and based in Pittsburgh, Pa., his professional clients included a variety of local corporate and non-profit institutions. Working mainly between the late 1960s and 1990s, Harris captured a multifaceted view of not only the corporate manufacturing world of Koppers and Alcoa, but also the local communities that allowed these institutions to thrive. Media includes gelatin silver prints, inkjet prints, 35mm, 120mm and 4x5 black and white and color negatives, 35mm black and white and color slides, 16mm film, videotape, digital video disk, audio cassettes, and manuscript materials.
Biography
Born in 1934 in Pittsburgh, Forrest "Bud" Harris graduated from Allderdice High School and briefly attended Carnegie Tech (now Carnegie Mellon University). In his early twenties, Bud worked at his father's used car lot as well as at a variety of other jobs. Photography became a passion and Bud began teaching himself the elements. From the beginning he developed a journalistic approach to photography and based his approach on telling a story. In 1959 Bud was hired by the Mt. Lebanon Times. It was the beginning of his life long career as a professional photographer. He moved from the Mt. Lebanon Times to Pittsburgh Plate Glass (PPG) where he became their official photographer for corporate promotions. After several years at PPG, he began his career as a freelance photographer.
Bud provided photographic and communication services for major and diverse clients throughout the US and Europe such as Alcoa, Gulf Oil, American Express, Magee Women's Hospital, Rutgers University, University of Pittsburgh, Social Security Administration and Business Week Magazine. Throughout his freelance career he provided photography, audio-visual and communication services to Koppers Company, and for seven of those years he served as a full-time employee.
Bud Harris won many national awards for his work including: Communications Arts' annual "Years Best Photography in Annual Report Category" for Magee-Women's Hospital Annual Report; three-time winner of "Best of Show Award" at the Three Rivers Arts Festival; a Golden Quill Award for "Best TV Spot" category for St. Peter's Child Development Center; and an ACE Award for "Public Service TV Spot" category for the University of Pittsburgh. He was also selected twice by Photo Maxima for inclusion in their international photo exhibit.
The Forrest "Bud" Harris Photograph Collection contains over 100,000 photographic prints and negatives, audio/visual items, and manuscript materials that document his career from the 1950s to 2007.
Following an exceptional career, Bud Harris passed away in 2009.
Scope and Content Notes
The Forrest "Bud" Harris Photographs is comprised of photographic prints, negatives, audio/visual, and manuscript materials that relate to his photographic projects. Items date from the 1950s to 2007 with the bulk of the collection dating between 1960 and 1999.
Harris worked for the University of Pittsburgh during the years of Chancellors Litchfield and Posvar. In addition to his professional collection of images, Harris was an accomplished documentary photographer. He produced projects documenting the lives of coal miners in West Virginia, garbage men in Pittsburgh, homelessness in Pittsburgh, and the Panther Hollow project. Included in this collection is a series of photographs taken on Sunday, April 7, 1968, three days after the assassination of Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. on the National Day of Mourning. A personal passion of Harris's was cycling; he photographed the sport extensively, especially BMX and road racing and was the co-founder of the Thrift Drug Classic race.
This collection includes work produced for Aluminum Company of America (Alcoa), Koppers Company (Koppers), Pittsburgh Plate Glass Company (PPG), American Express Bank (American Express), Archadeck, Walt Disney Company (Disney), Jones and Laughlin Steel Company (J&L Steel), Westinghouse Air Brake Company (WABCO), Mellon Bank, Time, Fortune, Business Week, Medical World News, Rutgers University, Boy Scouts of America, The University of Pittsburgh (Pitt), New York Times, and the Social Security Administration, among others.
Since the arrangement of this collection is partially dependent on format, there are gaps in the display of folder numbers. These gaps reflect the separation of 35mm and 120mm negatives.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Previous Citation
Forrest "Bud" Harris Photographs, ca. 1950s-2007, AIS.2013.05, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Acquisition Information
Gift of Ann Harris on July 11, 2013.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into eight series by format and chronologically by year. Arrangement of negatives, prints and slides follow the original numbers (date) assigned by the photographer. Job numbers used by Harris are also the date of image creation. For example, a job number of "62378" translates into June 23, 1978. However, there are "special topics" collections which Harris created after retirement that are arranged by a numbering system unique to that series.
Motion Pictures, DVDs, Audio Cassettes and Manuscript have been arranged by date, when available, and then by topic.
It is important to note that some items in the collection appear in both "special topics" collections as well as in their respective job-numbered folders.
Series I. Negatives, ca. 1950s-2000
Series II. Prints and Negatives, ca. 1950s-2004
Series III. Prints, ca. 1950s-2004
Series IV. Slides, ca. 1960s-2003
Series V. Motion Picture, ca. 1960s-2000
Series VI. DVDs, ca. 2000s-2008
Series VII. Audio Cassettes, 1976-1980
Series VIII. Manuscripts, ca. 1960s-2007
Existence and Location of Copies
The Harris family maintains a website with reproductions and information of Bud Harris's photographs.
Cycling; Bicycle motocross; BMX bikes; Business Week; Universities and colleges -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Butler County (Pa.); Poor People's Campaign; Polish Hill (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Point State Park (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Panther Hollow (Pittsburgh, Pa.); New York times; New York (N.Y.); Mister Rogers' neighborhood (Television program); Fortune; Greenfield (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Oakland (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Hill District (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Homewood (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Monroeville (Pa.); Mount Washington (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Photography, Industrial -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Sound recordings; Video recordings (physical artifacts); Motion pictures; Photo CDs; Slides (Photographs); Photographs; Photographers -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Negatives (Photographic); Education; Transportation; West Mifflin (Pa.); Turtle Creek (Pa.); Schenley Park (Pittsburgh, Pa.) -- Aerial photographs; South Side (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Squirrel Hill (Pittsburgh, Pa.) -- Aerial photographs; Pittsburgh (Pa.); Time; Sammartino, Bruno; Boy Scouts of America; Boston Marathon; Blue Cross Association; Beazer Environmental Services, Inc; Greenspan, Alan; Swiden, Art; Palmer, Arnold; Archadeck; American Express Bank; Aluminum Company of America; Civic Arena (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Chatham University; Chatham College; Cathedral of Learning (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Carnegie-Mellon University; Pittsburgh International Exhibition of Contemporary Art; Brown, Byrd; Carnegie International; Pittsburgh Zoo (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Pittsburgh Youth Symphony Orchestra; Pittsburgh Plate Glass Company; Fallingwater (Pa.); Eye and Ear Hospital (University of Pittsburgh); Moorhead, William S. (William Singer); Clifford Development Corporation; Balter House (Acme, Pa.); Byrom, Fletcher L.; Gateway Rehabilitation Center; John Golden Theatre (Organization: New York, N.Y.: 1937-); Harbison-Walker Refractories Company; Heinz Memorial Chapel (University of Pittsburgh); Senator John Heinz Pittsburgh Regional History Center (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Heinz Kerry, Teresa; Hickson Corporation; International Association of Business Communicators; Jones & Laughlin Steel Company; Joseph M. Katz Graduate School of Business; KDKA-TV (Television station: Pittsburgh, Pa.); Kaufmann's Department Store; Koppers Company; Magee Women's Hospital (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Mellon Bank; Levine, Mike; Nationality Rooms (Cathedral of Learning, Pittsburgh, Pa.); Oakland Planning and Development Corporation (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Oxford Development Group; Pennsylvania Association for the Blind; Flaherty, Peter F.; Pitt Panthers (Football team); Pittsburgh Marathon; University of Pittsburgh -- Students; WRS Motion Picture Laboratory; WQED (Television station: Pittsburgh, Pa.); Westinghouse Air Brake Company; Western Psychiatric Institute and Clinic (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Walt Disney Company; University of Pittsburgh; Thrift Drug Classic; Three Rivers Arts Festival (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Saint Peter's Child Development Centers (Pittsburgh, Pa.); United States. Social Security Administration; Smaller Manufacturers Council (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Rutgers University
- Negatives, ca. 1950s-2000; I.
  Scope and Content Notes
  This series contains negatives taken by Harris between the 1950s and 2000. The images were produced for both professional clients and personal interests. Formats include 35mm, 120mm and 4x5. Topics include Koppers, University of Pittsburgh, BMX, PPG, J&L Steel, Europe, Mellon Bank, Boston Marathon, Chatham College, Disney, Hickson, Thrift Drug Classic, Archadeck, Alcoa, Parkway Construction, Mr. Roger's Neighborhood, Fayette Bank, Levinson Steel, Social Security Administration, Burson-Marsteller, Oxford Development Corporation, and Magee Women's Hospital.
  - 35mm Negatives, ca. 1950s- 2000; 1.
    - ca. 1950s
      - PPG: 1, Girl in Fiberglass Boat, ca. 1950s (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Bud and Ryna, Jackie at Mellon Park, ca. 1950s (Box 4, Folder 4-5)
      - Bud in New York at Photo Maxima Exhibit, ca. 1950s (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Ryna and Alvin, Murray "Buzzy" Susser and Cat, ca. 1950s (Box 4, Folder 7-51)
      - Lens Test: 8mm Leica, 21mm Oxford Building, April 15, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - Ryna, ca. 1950s (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - ca. 1960s
      - Lens Test: 1, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Lens Test: 2, Symphony on Bridge, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Lens Test: 3, Stanley and Maria, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Lens Test: 4, Emil's Play, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Lens Test: 5, Maria, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Lens Test: 6, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Lens Test: 7, 85mm, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Lens Test: 8, 28mm Nikkor on M2 Leica, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Lens Test: 9, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Lens Test: 10, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Lens Test: 11, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Lens Test: 12, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Lens Test: 13, Pentax 35 sum., ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Lens Test: 14, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Lens Test: 15, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Lens Test: 16, Penns 35mm Sum., ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Lens Test: 17, Nikon B. Simon, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - Lens Test: 18, Blairs Sum. Bota M2A, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Lens Test: 19, 35 1.8 Nikkor, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 19)
      - Lens Test: 20, Nikon 21-28, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - Lens Test: 21, Canon 50-1.8 M2, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Lens Test: 22, 50-1.4 Canon, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - Lens Test: 23, Pentax, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 23)
      - Lens Test: 24, Nikon F:1.4, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 24)
      - Lens Test: 25, Jim Murray, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 25)
      - Lens Test: 26, 180 Soligor, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 26)
      - Little Girl at Zoo/Amusement Park, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 27)
      - Simma and Family, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 28)
      - Woman in an Office, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 29)
      - Bookstore and Camera Shop, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 30)
      - Bud and a Corvette, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 31)
      - Cat on a Fence, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 32)
      - Charlotte Lang, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 33-35)
      - Color Photographs, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 36)
      - Fallingwater: Inside of House, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 37)
      - Fisheye Lens, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 38)
      - Fisheye Lens: Cathedral of Learning, Mat and Hal Olsen, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 39)
      - Fisheye Lens: Office Views, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 40)
      - Dr. Francis and Wynn, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 41)
      - Highway, David S., ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 42)
      - Inside a Factory, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 43)
      - Jack Kintsler, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 44)
      - Man in a Factory, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 45)
      - Maria, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 46-47)
      - Maria and Bud; Pittsburgh in the Winter and Snow; Cathedral of Learning, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 48)
      - Mathew and Susie; Views of Pittsburgh, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 49)
      - Mathew 35 Sumicron; Colangelo House; Aerial Photographs, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 50)
      - Mat, Leslie, Joann; Views of Cathedral of Learning, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 51)
      - Pamela, 2 Girls at Carnegie Mellon, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 52)
      - People in a Living Room, Pittsburgh, Bud in Mirror, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 53)
      - Portraits, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 54)
      - Print Shop, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Roth Haus (Photograph of a Woman), ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Ryna at Playground, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 57-63)
      - Steel Workers on a Bridge, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 65-66)
      - Stony Brook University, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 67)
      - Volleyball 180mm, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 68)
      - West Mifflin Teachers Meeting, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 69)
      - Woman, Baby, Boat, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 70)
      - Woman in a Grocery Store, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 71)
      - Woman in an Office, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 72)
      - Wright Airlines; Maria and Sewing Machine; Rockwell Statue; House in North Hills, ca. 1960s (Box 5, Folder 73)
      - Mount Washington, Kaufmann's Department Store, Civic Arena, ca. 1960 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - 1962
      - Pitt Anniversary: #29 Mike Benedum at Pool, Roll 1, September 1962 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Pitt Anniversary: Roll 2, September 1962 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Pitt Anniversary: Beano Cook, Roll 3, September 1962 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Pitt Anniversary: 1800s Dance Costume, September 1962 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Pitt Anniversary: Roll 5, September 1962 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Pitt Anniversary: Nationality Rooms, September 1962 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Pitt Anniversary: Roll 7, September 1962 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Pitt Anniversary: Roll 8, September 1962 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Pitt Anniversary: Roll 9, September 1962 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Pitt Anniversary: Chancellor Litchfield, Governor David L. Lawrence and J. Albert, Roll 10, September 1962 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Pitt Anniversary: Mike Benedum, Roll 11, September 1962 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Pitt Anniversary: Roll 12, September 1962 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Pitt Anniversary: Mike Benedum, Roll 13, September 1962 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Pitt Anniversary: Roll 14-20, September 1962 (Box 6, Folder 14-20)
      - Pitt Anniversary: Student Rally, Roll 21-24, September 1962 (Box 6, Folder 21-24, 27)
      - Pitt Anniversary: Bon Fire Rally, September 1962 (Box 6, Folder 25-26)
      - Pitt Anniversary: Chancellor Litchfield and Governor David L. Lawrence, Roll 28L, September 1962 (Box 6, Folder 28)
      - Pitt Anniversary: Roll 29-33, September 1962 (Box 6, Folder 29-33)
    - 1963
      - PPG Chemical Plant, April 1963 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - 1964
      - J&L Steel Research; Bill Babyack; Al Ruck #6, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - Inside Library, January 21, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      - Minority Program: Roll 1, March 17, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Minority Program: Roll 3, March 17, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      - Carnegie: Roll 4, March 17, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      - Work Project: Roll 5, March 17, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - Carnegie 3 Boys and Sculpture: Roll 6, March 17, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      - Carnegie Graduation: Roll 7, March 17, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 22)
      - Sculpture Reproduction: Roll 8, March 17, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 23)
      - Larry Heller Wedding (Pitt Faculty), December 21, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 58, 60-62)
    - 1966
      - Lois Muss, August 22, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 1-3)
    - 1968
      - Miami, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 4-6)
      - J&L Steel Hazelwood Rolling Mill Research Lab, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 7-8)
      - Black Power on WALO; Mat 4 Years Old; Rangefinder Test, May 1968 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Three Rivers Arts Festival, May 1968 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Rangefinder Test Nikon SP., May 1968 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Fisheye Lens: Western Virginia, Hillman Library, June 1968 (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - Mitey Lite Test, October 1968 (Box 8, Folder 13)
      - Great Race J & L Steel, October 1968 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Jack Brown's Store; Tech Scenes, October 1968 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - Tech with Pitt in Background; Maria in Shadyside Through a Glass Sculpture; Mat and Blocks in Room; Jack Brown in Store, October 1968 (Box 8, Folder 16)
      - Century Club with Dr. Henry T. Bahnson, December 1968 (Box 8, Folder 16)
      - Nancy Sieverts, December 1968 (Box 8, Folder 17)
      - Mat's Christmas, December 25, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - 1969
      - Huck and Hannah, January 1969 (Box 8, Folder 19)
      - Pitt Sit-In, February 1969 (Box 8, Folder 20-21)
      - Paul's Negatives; Washington D.C., March 1969 (Box 8, Folder 22)
      - Porsche & Mat at P. Plant for Art, May 19, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 23)
      - Hospital Planning Association; Reiner, July 17, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 24)
      - Y-IKC, July 17, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 25-26)
      - Harold Milton Accident; Hippie Pals; Bubble, July 1969 (Box 8, Folder 27)
      - Paul's Negatives, August 1969 (Box 8, Folder 28)
      - Baby, August 1969 (Box 8, Folder 29)
      - Bud and Bunny; Smog Over the City, September 1969 (Box 8, Folder 30)
      - Umbrella Test; Maria, September 1969 (Box 8, Folder 31)
      - J&L Steel Research: John Stewart, March 21, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 29)
    - 1970
      - Flagstaff Band Panorama 10,000 People; Hippy Park Panorama; Byrd Brown and Molly Yard and Father Charles Owen Rice at Freedom Corner; Leica 28mm, ca. 1970s (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Koppers: Swimming Pool, February 12, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Koppers: Good Fish Tanks, February 12, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Koppers: Piling, February 12, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Koppers, February 12, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Koppers: Piling, February 12, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Koppers, February 12, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 6-7)
      - Marshall Jack Baker, March 1970 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Social Security Administration, March 20, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 9-20)
      - Computer School: Finance, April 1, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 21)
      - Computer School: Medical, April 1, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 22)
      - Computer School: Airport, April 1, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 22-24)
      - Computer School, April 1, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 25-27)
      - Koppers: Southern Trip, October 5, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 46-47)
      - Great Tank Shot, October 15, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 48)
      - Wood Gas Station, October 15, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 49)
      - Koppers: Caminating Plant, October 26, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 56-61)
      - Fayette Bank, November 1, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 66-67)
      - Koppers: Sam Kauffmann; Shrink Wrap, December 28, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 68-69)
    - 1971
      - Scoreboard, January 4, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 1-6)
      - Koppers: Roofs, C, ca. 1970s (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Computer Tech (Santel Agency), January 20, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 10-13)
      - Namir: 1-15, 19, January 24, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 14-28, 32)
      - Namir: 18, Feldman Kahn Sutton, January 24, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 31)
      - Namir: 16-17, Color, Jenny, January 24, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 29-30)
      - Office, February 2, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 33-36)
      - Steinberg, Marshall, Balter, Blum: Architecture, February 3, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 37-48)
      - Koppers: Test Burn, February 4, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 49)
      - Pickling Plant, February 16, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 50-52)
      - Steinberg House and Peter Berndtson, February 21, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 57-58)
      - The Balter House, February 25, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 64-66)
      - Marshall Homes, February 28, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 70-71)
      - ACLD Banquet, March 12, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 72-75)
      - Peter Steinberg: Wide Shots Exterior, March 18, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 76)
        See Also
        See also job number 22171 (February 21, 1971)
      - Widelux: Steinberg Interior, March 18, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 77)
        See also job number 221711 (or, February 21, 1971).
      - Peter Berndtson, March 18, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 78)
      - Portraits, March 30, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 79-81)
      - Koppers: Gazebo, May 17, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 5-7, 12)
      - Mrs. Freidman, May 21, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - Koppers: Meadows Gazebo, June 3, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 17, 21, 27)
      - Neville Island Plant, June 4, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 32-35)
      - Fayette Bank, Feldman and Kahn, June 24, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 37-45)
      - Koppers: Fletcher L. Byrom, July 8, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 46-54)
      - Koppers: Piling Ideal Toy Company, New Jersey Harbor Area, July 19, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 62-67)
      - Koppers: Tar Roof, July 23, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 3-4, 10-15)
      - Koppers: Columbus Ohio; Gas Station Marathon Oil; House of Wolman; Lite Risers, August 3, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 28, 35, 37, 40, 56, 61-64,)
      - School of Computer Technology, August 6, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 69-73)
      - Koppers: Miss Torch, August 12, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 74-76)
      - Allstate Industry, August 25, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 1-3)
      - Lou Sautal, Consolidation Coal Company, September 1, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - GRSW P.A.T Display, September 10, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 9-10)
      - Koppers: New England, September 14, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 12-13, 17-29, 48)
      - Levinson Steel, September 28, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 52-54)
      - Re-Shoot, October 1, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 58)
      - TAC Air The Agency, October 1, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 63, 67, 71, 75-77)
      - TAC Air The Agency, October 1, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 1-3, 16-19)
      - WRS- Motion Picture Equipment Company, October 14, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 20)
      - Koppers: Butler County, Special School, October 22, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 22-23)
      - Koppers: Orlando, November 1, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 35-44)
      - L.B. Foster, Fast Track, December 1, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 45-51)
      - Fayette Bank Port., Feld and Kahn Agency, December 3, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 52-65)
      - Le Page Glue Meeting, December 21, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 66-69)
      - Motorcycle, Mat and Suzy, October 27, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 40)
    - 1972
      - Mat and Susie in Miami, Florida, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Dave Westhead, January 18, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Koppers: Mobile Homes; Dayton, Ohio, January 19, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 3, 7, 11, 15)
      - Home for AIP Child: 2 Portraits, February 3, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 16)
      - Koppers: Portraits and Candids, February 8, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 17-31)
      - Wenman Schmidt; I.M.G.; Judy Fender Nurses, February 11, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 33-35)
      - Koppers: Walter Wellborn High School, Anniston, Alabama, February 24, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 36-48)
      - Lando: Penny, March 10, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 59-67)